They walk among us in disguise
Fake names and faces spreading lies
In the digital crowds they skate
Masters of a phantom base
Who's real and who's a masquerade
In this wild book parade
We spin around till the truth bends
Can you spot your real friends?
Hiding in virtual shape
A perfect storm they've made
Questions stir inside our head
Is this life or algorithm fed?
Who's real and who's a masquerade
In this wild book parade
We spin around till the truth bends
Can you spot your real friends?
They speak in scripted code so tight
Unseen in the dead of night
Unmask them if you dare
Yet they vanish in thinner
Who's real and who's a masquerade
In this wild book parade
We spin around till the truth bends
Can you spot your real friends?
Who's real and who's a masquerade
In this wild book parade
We spin around till the truth bends
Can you spot your real friends?
Who's real and who's a masquerade
In this wild book parade
Turn around till the truth ends
Can you spot your real friends?
You spin around till the truth ends
Your friends
Your real friends
Yeah